Dominic Apolo

▲ dominic.apolo03@gmail.com **人** (507) 279-4270 **♦** Austin, MN 55912

k dom2dev.pythonanywhere.com/ github.com/dom2polo in linkedin.com/in/dominic-apolo

Profile

Passionate Karen Computer Science graduate (expected May 2024) dedicated to serving the Karen community. Committed to leveraging technical expertise and cultural understanding to provide invaluable assistance and support. Striving to bridge technology and societal needs for a more inclusive community.

Education

08/2020 - 05/2024St. Cloud, MN

St. Cloud State University B.S. Computer Science (GPA: 3.5)

Professional Experience

05/2022 - 12/2022Chanhassen, MN

Software Engineer Intern

Emerson

- Managed 20+ change requests with precision, utilizing the Kanban agile methodology for streamlined execution.
- Elevated inter-departmental communication, a key driver for achieving successful project goals.

01/2023 - 05/2023Roseville, MN

Out of School Youth Worker

Roseville Area Schools

- Facilitating engaging activities to keep children entertained and stimulated during their time in my care, fostering a positive and enriching environment.
- Monitoring and ensuring the safety and well-being of children within the K-6 age group before school starts and after classes end.

Skills

• Office Suites, Bi-lingual, Problem-solving, Cross-cultural, Collaboration, Data-Management, Written Communication, Tech-savvy, Adaptability, Strong Work Ethic

Organizations

08/2023 - present St. Cloud, MN

Karen Student United Association (KSUA)

Secretary

- Scheduled, organized, and documented club meetings, ensuring continuity and facilitating communication and attendance.
- Provided valuable insights and recommendations, drawing from personal experiences and community perspectives.

Volunteer Experience

08/2020 - present Austin, MN

Cenchrea Karen Baptist Church

Event Assistant Volunteer

- Supported tech team with sound system setup and contributed event ideas, while also participating in fundraising efforts.
- Offered transportation assistance to the Karen community within the church.

03/2024 Austin, MN

Immigration Law Center of Minnesota

- Checked IDs and helped close cases
- Made sure clients were assigned correctly by organizing and searching for their IDs.